{
    "id": "78f6953ab7814f478ca301164d1df8ff",
    "title": "Editing Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They went out despite of the rain.",
            "description": "The correct preposition is despite.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "of",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a5efac26f9c415c98e71d07f438ed71"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sonia, who is my neighbor, she is a writer.",
            "description": "A clause needs just one subject.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "she",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea6c0d17e1e84a6180fbcadb728e1570"
        },
        {
            "question": "No matter what that I do, he is never happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e837f45e3ac43f08a35d052fa010f30"
        },
        {
            "question": "I almost nearly wish I had stayed home.",
            "description": "Nearly is similar to almost. It is mainly used to suggest progress towards a goal.",
            "answers": [
                "almost",
                "nearly",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61ab1bc50b1b445f9da99504c4a65cd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is nearly never at home.",
            "description": "We cannot use nearly with negative words like never.",
            "answers": [
                "nearly",
                "never",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05c72e9de2e9457aa8ced44bfbb707f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have visited them a fortnight ago.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect with past time expressions like 'a fortnight ago'.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "visited",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "811b0601f4ba49d3957f3497489e258b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better not to disturb dad.",
            "description": "After had better the infinitive is used without to.",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "better",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c80c2f0d389c4268a3a3281527308cd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want that you to tell me exactly what happened.",
            "description": "The sentence should read: I want you to tell me exactly what happened.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "to",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baef1c3605144f9f94fb2d275d544ac1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They made me to retract my statement.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after make.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "to",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50117fe9d7b1497087732537adc72db5"
        },
        {
            "question": "As well as he breaking his leg, John hurt his arm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a78f37bced604289ba052d845527dd0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house where I live in is very small.",
            "description": "We use where instead of that...in.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "in",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c488bfc5f29c4158a7cbc1dd3c1035b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw him to come out of the house.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after see.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60dd0ed1ac404d5b8fe6f500fdc88c66"
        }
    ]
}